在我们创建content provider之前
Before we start creating our content provider,
我们先回顾一下weather contract
it's time to go back to our weather
我们将使用weather contract
contract. We're going to use the weather contract,
定义database和content provider
for both database definitions and content provider definitions.
我们包括的这些URI会公开数据和界面
These are the URIs that our contract will expose for a data and view. Some of
有些URL会返回一些列表或者项目目录
them return a list or directory of items.
还有一些会返回单个的项
And some of them return as single item.
URI第一部分所描述的内容是系统如何从不同的应用中
The first part of the URI is the content authority which is how the system
分辨出URL的，就像域名
disambiguate URIs from different application, similar to the
和网站之间的关系一样
relationship between a domain name and its website.
这一串用于授权的简单字符
A convenient string to use for the content
是这个应用的包名
authority is the package name of the app.
让我们回到我们的weather contract，我们将
Let's return to our weather contract. We'll add
为content provider增加CONTENT_AUTHORITY和BASE_CONTENT_URI
the CONTENT_AUTHORITY and the BASE_CONTENT_URI for our content
在我们的weather contract代码的前面部分
provider to the beginning of our weather
接下来，我们会在添加一些字符到
contract. Next, we'll add strings to the base
URI的基础路径中。每一个URI
path of our URIs. Each URI essentially points
实际上都指向一张不同的表，对于每一张表
to a different table. For each of our
location entry和weather entry，我们都为每张表
tables, location entry, and weather entry, we
创建了相对应的content URI
create a content URI that represents the base location for each table. Now,
我们还会在location和weather contract中增加一些magical value
we'll add some magical value to the location and weather entry contracts.
这些包含特殊MIME类型的前缀表示
These contain special MIME type prefixes that indicate that
这个URI要么返回一个目录，列表项要么返回
the URI either returns a directory, list of items,
一个单一项。现在，我们将在weather entry中增加
or a single item. Now, we're going to add some
URI builder和decoder 功能，
URI builders and decoder functions in weather entry. It's
这是很方便的，因为当知道真实的URI编码后，
convenient to have this as it makes fewer places
它使得你的代码更少
in your code aware of the actual URI encoding,
在contract知识中记住这个知识点，如果你只是
keeping this knowledge in the contract. If you're just
将有一个标准的 integer primary key 的URI
going to have a URI with a standard integer
这是用来区分项目查询
primary key, which is a typical way of distinguishing between
或者列表项查询的典型方式
a query for item or the query for a list
也可以使用ContentUris.withAppendedId 函数
of items, one can use the content URIs with appended
Strings，比如说设置地理位置，可以
id function. Strings, such as a location setting, can be
用appendPath函数，我们也可以使用这些函数
appended with the append path function. We can also use these
增加可能有用的查询参数，在这个例子中
functions to add potentially useful query parameters. In this case,
我们使用一个startDate作为一个查询参数。
we use a query parameter for the start date. Query
当我们有一个固定的，
parameters are useful for when we have a fixed database
并且是有限的参数查询数据库时，查询参数是很有用的
query that we want to have some limited parameterization
在这个例子中，这是这链接这两张表中参数
for. In this case, it will be a parameter for
最后，我们有
our join between the two tables. Finally, we have
生成都两部分都包含
this function that builds a two part URI that contains
location 和date segments的URI的函数。除此以外，还有
both location and date segments. Below this, we have
其他辅助函数用来帮助解码URI结构，通过
helper functions that help decode the URI structure. This hides
我们的代码将URI结构隐藏了起来，并且
the URI structure form our code as well and
将所有的知识都放在了contract中
places all the knowledge in one place within the contract.